Artur Rodzinski Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Correspondence, 1931-1976, bulk 1938-1953 (Box 1-11)
  - Turner, Thomas, 1943 (Box 10/30)
  - Turner, Tyler see Columbia Records, Inc.
  - Tyborowski, C., 1939 (Box 10/31)
  - Uhlfelder, Gerado see Organización de conciertos gérard
  - Ulehla, Ludmila, 1942 (Box 10/32)
  - Union Mutual Fire Insurance Company (Montpelier, Vt.), 1942 (Box 10/33)
  - United Artists Publishing Company, 1947 (Box 10/34)
  - United Newspapers Magazine Corporation see Muriel Francis
  - United Mutual see Liberty Mutual Insurance Company
  - United States. Bureau of the Public Debt, 1949-1950 (Box 10/35)
  - United States. Dept. of the Treasury, 1944 (Box 10/36)
  - United States. Dept. of the Treasury. Fiscal Service see United States. Bureau of the Public Debt
  - United States. Embassy, 1934 (Box 10/37)
  - United States. Embassy (Yugoslavia), 1952 (Box 10/38)
  - United States. Foreign Service, 1949-1950 (Box 10/39)
  - United States. Office of War Information, 1945 (Box 10/40)
  - United States. War Finance Division, 1944 (Box 10/41)
  - Universal Recording Co. Inc., 1942 (Box 10/42)
  - University of Miami, 1951 (Box 10/43)
  - University of Miami. Symphony Orchestra, 1949 (Box 10/44)
  - University of Michigan. University Musical Society, 1942 (Box 10/45)
  - Usigli, Gastone, 1943-1950 (Box 10/46)
  - USSR Society for Cultural Relations with Foreign Countries see Vsesoiuznoe obshchestvo kul’turnoĭ sviazi s zagranitseĭ (Soviet Union)
  - Valdemar, 1948 (Box 10/47)
  - Valentine, May, 1949 (Box 10/48)
  - Valmarana see Teatro La Fenice
  - Van Rensselaer Cox, Sylvia see Cox, Sylvia van Rensselaer
  - Van Vactor, David, 1940 (Box 10/49)
  - Vardell, Charles Gildersleeve, 1943 (Box 10/50)
  - Venture Sales Co., 1942 (Box 10/51)
  - Venturini, Anna see Radio audizioni Italia
  - Vienesa, Endecha, n.d. (Box 10/52)
  - Vienot, Mrs. Y.M., 1951 (Box 10/53)
  - Viggiani, Pela Empreza Viggiani-Dante see Jack Adams and Co. see Elkan-Vogel Co.
  - Violin Teachers Guild, 1943 (Box 10/54)
  - Vitalis, George, 1948 (Box 10/55)
  - Viteri Lafronte, Rosa de see George M. Horn Company
  - Vogel, Adolph see Jack Adams and Co. see Elkan-Vogel Co.
  - VOKS see Vsesoiuznoe obshchestvo kul’turnoĭ sviazi s zagranitseĭ (Soviet Union)
  - Volpe, Marie see University of Miami. Symphony Orchestra
  - Von Hallberg, Gene, 1945 (Box 10/56)
  - Vosburgh, Carl J., 1934-1935 see also Barkentin, Marjorie see also Cleveland Orchestra see also Fitelson and Mayers see also Musical Arts Association (Cleveland, Ohio) see also Radamsky, Sergei (Box 10/57)
  - Votto, Pariso see Teatro comunale di Firenze see Radio audizioni Italia
  - Vsesoiuznoe obshchestvo kul’turnoĭ sviazi s zagranitseĭ (Soviet Union), 1934-1944 (Box 10/58)
  - Vyner, Louis, 1949 (Box 10/59)
  - V miscellaneous, 1950 (Box 10/60)
  - W. Colston Leigh, Inc., 1942-1945 (Box 10/61)
  - Wagenaar, Bernard, 1943-1947 (Box 10/62)
  - Wagner, Charles L., 1944 (Box 10/63)
  - Wagner, Friedelind, 1942 (Box 10/64)
  - Wagner, Joseph, 1943 (Box 10/65)
  - Walcott, Mrs. John W. see Walcott, Muriel
  - Walcott, Muriel, 1949-1950 see also Sweeney, John S., Jr. (Box 10/66)
  - Wallenstein, Alfred see Los Angeles Philharmonic Orchestra
  - Wallerstein, Edward see Columbia Records, Inc.
  - Walpole, Floyd F. see Civic Symphony Society (Denver, Colo.)
  - Walter, Bruno, 1945 (Box 10/67)
  - Walter, Nelly see Columbia Concerts Corporation (Columbia Broadcasting System)
  - War Production Board, 1945 (Box 10/68)
  - Warburg, James Paul, 1939-1940 (Box 10/69)
  - Ware, Harriet, 1942 (Box 10/70)
  - Warner, John A., 1940 (Box 10/71)
  - Warner, Philip, 1947 (Box 10/72)
  - Warnow, Mark, 1944 (Box 10/73)
  - Warszawskie Towarzystwo Muzyczne im. Stanisłlawa Moniuszki see Maliszewski, W.
  - Wasia, n.d. (Box 10/74)
  - Watson, Archibald R. see Troychack, Edith L.
  - Wayne, W. see Organización de conciertos gérard
  - Weber, Henry, 1940 (Box 10/75)
  - Webster, Mrs. N.C., 1944 (Box 10/76)
  - Wecker, Karl see Hollywood Bowl Association
  - Weigl, Mrs. Karl see Weigl, Vally
  - Weigl, Vally, 1945 (Box 10/77)
  - Weinhold, Kurt see Columbia Concerts Corporation (Columbia Broadcasting System)
  - Weiss, Paul M. see Carl Fischer Inc.
  - Welch, James T. see Muriel Francis
  - Wells, Carter, 1950 (Box 10/78)
  - Wells, Summer, 1941 (Box 10/79)
  - Wertheim, Arnold see Acro Associates, Inc.
  - Wetherell, Ward E. see Massachusetts. Dept. of Corporations and Taxation
  - Wheeler & Taylor, Inc., 1942 (Box 10/80)
  - Wheeler-Imparato, Ester Belle see Imparato, Giovanni
  - White, Charles Lafayette see Sturdy, L. Alice
  - White, Clarence Cameron, 1943 (Box 10/81)
  - White, Sister Mary see Surrey Clinic
  - Whitman, H.N. see Hornblower & Weeks
  - Wien, Walter see United States. Embassy (Yugoslavia)
  - Wiener, Elmer A., 1949 (Box 10/82)
  - Wiener Philharmoniker, 1952 (Box 10/83)
  - Wieter, Helga, 1951, Two photographs of Wieter. (Box 10/84)
  - Wiley, John Cooper see United States. Embassy
  - Wilkins, John M. see John F. White, Inc.
  - Wilkomirski, Michael, 1942 (Box 10/85)
  - William L. Stein, Inc. see Poleri, David
  - William Morris Agency, 1945 (Box 10/86)
  - Willy-Overland Motors, 1949 (Box 10/87)
  - Wilson, A.E. see United States. Bureau of the Public Debt
  - Winsch, M.J. see Moore-McCormack Lines, Inc.
  - Winson, S.A., 1949 (Box 10/88)
  - [Wishard], Sciff, 1942 (Box 10/89)
  - Witek, Eugene, n.d. (Box 10/90)
  - Witkowski, Franiszek, 1942 (Box 10/91)
  - Wittell, Chester, 1945 (Box 10/92)
  - Wolf & Davis, 1948-1950 (Box 10/93)
  - Wolf, Walter B. see Wolf & Davis
  - Wolfe, Florence see National Concert and Artists Corporation
  - Wolfes, Felix, 1945 (Box 10/94)
  - Wolpin, Edward A. see Heilner, Irwin
  - Woods, Baldwin M. see Music Corporation of America
  - Wooldridge, John de L., 1944-1945 (Box 10/95)
  - Woulff, Mr., 1953 (Box 10/96)
  - Wright, Mrs. Frank Lloyd see Wright, Olgivanna Lloyd
  - Wright, Olgivanna Lloyd, 1950 (Box 10/97)
  - Wymetal, William, 1942 (Box 10/98)
  - W miscellaneous, 1948 (Box 10/99)
  - Xauώ, Ernesto, 1950 (Box 10/100)
  - Yardumian, Richard, 1945 (Box 11/1)
  - Young People’s Record Club, Inc., n.d. (Box 11/2)
  - Zanin, Lt., 1951 (Box 11/3)
  - Zaremba, Sylvia, n.d. (Box 11/4)
  - Zayas, N. L. Hernandez, 1950 (Box 11/5)
  - Zeisl, Eric, 1943-1947 (Box 11/6)
  - Zemachson, Arnold, 1942-1943 (Box 11/7)
  - Zerbel, Gladys see Hollywood Bowl Association
  - Zilboorg, Gregory, 1939 (Box 11/8)
  - Zillerbach, Harold see San Francisco (Calif.). Art Commission
  - Zimbalist, Mary Louise Curtis Bok, 1933-1943 (Box 11/9)
  - Ziolkowski, C.S. see Polish Arts Club
  - Zirato, Bruno, 1945-1949 see also Maier, Guy see also New York Philharmonic see also Walter, Bruno (Box 11/10)
  - Zuckerman, Besse see Bay Cities Music Association
  - Zuckerman, Mrs. Joseph see Bay Cities Music Association
  - Zusser, Maurice M., 1947 (Box 11/11)
- Annotated Music, circa 1868-1956, bulk 1932-1947 (Box 13-43; 52-59)
  This series is comprised of printed music, photocopied music and a few manuscripts. The majority of the music consists of orchestral, chamber and choral works; the bulk of the publications are in English, in addition to German, Polish, Russian, French and Japanese. These scores have been annotated with conductor marks, stamps, and composers’ inscriptions. A few of the scores have pasteovers. Printed music that was not annotated was removed from the collection and cataloged separately in the Music Division’s general collections.
  The series is arranged alphabetically by composer and then by title.
  - Albéniz, Isaac
    - Fête dieu à séville. [S.l.: s.n., n.d.] (Box-folder 13/5-6)
      - Printed full score, 47 p. (Box-folder 13/5)
      - Copyist and photocopy parts, Second movement in “Iberia” (Box-folder 13/6)
  - Altisent, Juan
    - Concierto: para oboe y orquesta. Barcelona: [s.n.], 1954, 34 p. (Box-folder 52/1)
  - Andreae, Volkmar
    - Kleine suite, für Orchester, op. 27. Leipzig: F.E.C. Leuckart, [1910-1919?], 46 p. (Box-folder 14/1)
  - Andriessen, Hendrik
    - Variaties op een thema van Couperin: voor fluit met begleiding van strijkorkest harp. Amsterdam: Donemus, 1944, Photocopy; [34] p. (Box-folder 14/2)
  - Antheil, George
    - [Symphonies, no. 5]
      - Fifth symphony: (“Joyous”) [S.l.: s.n.], 1947-48, Photocopy; 117 p. (Box-folder 52/2)
  - Bach, Carl Philipp Emanuel
    - Concerto (D-dur) instrumentée pour petit orchestre. Berlin: Edition Russe De Musique, 1911, 26 p. (Box-folder 14/3)
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian
    - Bist du bei mir. [S.l.: s.n., n.d.], Arranger’s holograph; 4 p.; Arranged by Stanleigh P. Friedman. (Box-folder 14/4)
    - [Orgelbüchlein]
      - Due chorali = zwei choräle. New York: Universal-Edition, 1925, 12 p.; Transcribed from organ for orchestra by Vittorio Gui. (Box-folder 14/5)
    - Our father in heaven...
      - Bach, Chorale: our father in heaven (vater unser im Himmelreich) [page 1] New York: Associated Music Publishers, 1937, 4 p.; Arranged for string orchestra by Arcady Dubensky.; 2 copies. (Box-folder 14/6)
    - The passion of our Lord according to St. Matthew. Boston: Oliver Ditson Company, 1916, xii, 262 p.; Piano arrangements by Julius Stern and Robert Franz.; Text translated and adapted by John Sullivan Dwight.; Revised and edited by Louis Koemmenich. (Box-folder 14/7)
    - [Präludium und Fuge, organ, BWV 534, F minor; arr.]
      - Prelude und fugue in F minor (S. 534) San Diego, Calif.: Music Graphics Press, 1978, Photocopy; 46 p.; Transcribed for orchestra by Eugene Zádor. (Box-folder 52/3)
    - Ricercare a 6 voci aus dem “Musikalischen Opfer” über ein thema Friedrichs des Grossen. Berlin: Ed. Bote & G. Bock, 1930, 16 p. (Box-folder 14/8)
    - [Sonaten und Partiten, violin, BWV 1001-1006. Partita, no. 3. Gavotte en rondeau; arr.]
      - Gavotte en rondeau: from the sixth violin sonata of Johann Sebastian Bach. [S.l.: s.n., n.d.], Arrangers’s holograph; 13 p.; Arranged by Stanleigh P. Friedman. (Box-folder 14/9)
    - St. Matthew passion: chorus 1 “Come, ye daughters” [S.l.: s.n., n.d.], 25 p.; Abbreviated version. (Box-folder 14/10)
    - [Suites, orchestra, BWV 1067, B minor]
      - Suite in H moll: für Flöte, zwei Violinen, Viola, Violoncell und Contrabass. Leipzig: F.E.C. Leuckart, [n.d.], 25 p.; Ausgeführtem Accompagnement versehen seinem Freunde Julius Schäffer zugeeignet von Robert Franz. (Box-folder 14/11)
    - Toccata, (C-dur). I. Präludium. II. Adagio. III. Fuga. Wien: Universal-Edition A.G., 1930, 64 p. (Box-folder 15/1)
  - Baron, Maurice
    - [Ode to democracy. Vocal score. English]
      - Ode to democracy: a musical setting of Lincoln’s Gettysburg Address. New York: M. Baron Co., 1947, [26] p. (Box-folder 15/2)
  - Bartók, Béla
    - [Magyar parasztdalok. Selections]
      - Ungarische Bauernlieder = Magyar parasztdalok = Chansons paysannes hongroises. Wien: Universal-Edition, 1937, 30 p. (Box-folder 15/3)
    - [Music, celesta, percussion, string orchestra]
      - Musik für Saiteninstrumente, Schlagzeug und Celesta: in 4 Sätzen. Wien: Universal-Edition A.G., 1937, 119 p. (Box-folder 15/4)
  - Beethoven, Ludwig van
    - Andante con variaioni thema Sonate [front cover] [S.l.: s.n, n.d.], Copyists; 74 p.; v. Jos. Klein (Box-folder 15/5)
    - [Symphonies, no. 3, op. 55, E♭ major]
      - Symphonien für grosses Orchester, no. 3, Es dur, op. 55 Dritte Symphonie, op. 55, Eroica [page 3] Leipzig: Breitkopf & Härtel, [n.d.], 96 p. or p. (113)-(206) (Box-folder 15/6)
    - [Symphonies, no. 9, op. 125, D minor]
      - Symphonie für grosses Orchester, no. 9, D moll, op. 125. Leipzig: Breitkopf & Härtel, [n.d.], 276 p. (Box-folder 16/1)
    - [Symphonies, no. 9, op. 125, D minor]
      - Symphonie nr. 9 D moll - D minor - Rè mineur, op. 125. Leipzig: Breitkopf & Härtel, [n.d.], Parts. (Box-folder 16/2, 17/1)
  - Berlioz, Hector
    - Marche Troyenne: tirée de l’opéra les Troyens á Carthage. New York: Edwin F. Kalmus, [n.d.], Photocopy; 35 p. (Box-folder 18/1)
    - [Troyens. Chasse royale et orage]
      - Symphonie descriptive. New York: Edwin F. Kalmus, [n.d.], Photocopy; 32 p. (Box-folder 18/2)
  - Bernstein, Leonard
    - The age of anxiety: symphony no. 2 for piano and orchestra (after Auden) Symphony no. 2 (The age of anxiety) [front cover] New York: [s.n.], 1949, Photocopy; 2 v. Part I, Part II; “Reproduced by Presto Reproductions.” (Box-folder 59/1)
  - Bilotti, Anton
    - Roman suite: for string orchestra. [S.l.: s.n., n.d.], Photocopy; [38] p. (Box-folder 18/3)
  - Bliss, Arthur, Sir
    - Checkmate: a ballet in one scene with a prologue. London: Novello and Company, 1937, 92 p. (Box-folder 18/4)
    - Concert suite from Checkmate. London: Novello and Company, 1938, 168 p. (Box-folder 18/5)
    - [Concerto, piano, B♭ major]
      - Concerto for piano and orchestra. London: Novello and Company, 1940, 100 p. (Box-folder 18/6)
        Piano solo with orchestra arranged for second piano.
        Commissioned by the British Council for the British Week at the New York World’s Fair 1939.
  - Bloch, Suzanne
    - To the children: elegy for string orchestra To the war children: elegy for string orchestra [paper inserted] New York: [s.n.], 1944, Photocopy; 10 p. (Box-folder 18/7)
  - Brahms, Johannes
    - [Symphony, no. 1, op. 68, C minor]
      - Symphonie (C moll) für grosses Orchester. Berlin: N. Simrock, [1877], 100 p. (Box-folder 19/1)
    - [Symphony, no. 3, op. 90, F major]
      - Dritte symphonie (F dur) für grosses Orchester. Berlin: N. Simrock, [1884], 109 p. (Box-folder 19/2)
  - Burleigh, Cecil
    - Symphonic trilogy: Symphony no. 1 (Creation), Symphony no. 2 (Prophecy), Symphony no. 3 (Revelation) [S.l.: s.n.], 1945, Photocopy; 3 v. 68 p., 77 p., 52 p. (Box-folder 52/4)
  - Cadman, Charles Wakefield
    - American suite for string orchestra. New York: Composers Press Inc., 1938, 16 p. (Box-folder 19/3)
  - Carpenter, John Alden
    - Serenade. [S.l.: s.n.], 1948, Photocopy; 45 p. (Box-folder 59/2)
  - Cesana, Otto
    - [American symphony, no. 2]
      - Second American symphony. New York: Edgar Stillman-Kelley Society, 1937, 155 p. (Box-folder 19/4)
  - Chabrier, Emanuel
    - España: Rapsodie pour orchestre. Paris: Enoch Frères &Costallat, [n.d.], 61 p. (Box-folder 19/5)
  - Copland, Aaron
    - Quiet city, by Aaron Copland, for strings, trumpet and English horn (oboe) New York: Boosey & Hawkes Inc., 1941, 15 p. (Box-folder 19/6)
  - Couperin, François
    - [Sultane. Gravement: arr.]
      - Overture and allegro: from la sultane suite. Philadelphia: Elkan-Vogel, 1944, 23 p.; Orchestration and free transcription by Darius Milhaud. (Box-folder 19/7)
  - Cowell, Henry
    - American pipers. [S.l.: s.n.], 1943, Photocopy; 15 p.; Written at the request of the League of Composers for Dr. Artur Rodzinski and the New York Philharmonic Symphony. (Box-folder 52/5)
    - Concerto for piano and orchestra. Partition d’orchestre. Paris: M. Senart, 1913, 63 p. (Box-folder 19/8)
    - Hymn and fuguing tune no. 2, for string orchestra. New York: Associated Music Publishers, 1944, Photocopy; 7 p. (Box-folder 19/9)
    - Symphonic set: for symphony orchestra, in five movements. New York: Arrow Music, 1939, 57 p.; Symphonic opus 17.; 2 copies. (Box-folder 19/10)
  - Damrosch, Walter
    - An Abraham Lincoln song: for baritone solo, chorus of liberated slaves and orchestra: on Walt Whitman’s poem O Captain! My Captain! New York: M. Witmark & Sons, 1936, 24 p. (Box-folder 20/1)
    - [Man without a country. Vocal score]
      - The man without a country. New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., 1937, 167 p.; Libretto by Arthur Guiterman. (Box-folder 20/2)
  - Daniels, Mabel Wheeler
    - Pastoral ode for flute and strings. New York: J. Fischer & Bro., 1940, 27 p. (Box-folder 20/3)
  - Debussy, Claude
    - La Mer: trois esquisses symphoniques partition d’orchestre. Paris: A. Durand & Fils, 1905, 137 p. (Box-folder 20/4)
    - [Poèmes de Ch. Baudelaire. Let jet d’eau: arr.]
      - Le jet d’eau, poème de Charles Baudelaire. Paris: A. Durand & Fils, 1907, Full score and parts (Box-folder 20/5)
  - Delius, Frederick
    - 2 Stücke für kleines Orchester. I. On hearing the first cuckoo in spring. Beim ersten Kuckuckaruf im Frühling. II. Summer night on the river. Sommernacht am flusse Partitur. Cöln am Rhein: Tischer & Jagenbert, 1913, 14 p. (Box-folder 20/6)
    - [Village Romeo and Juliet. The walk to the Paradise Garden]
      - Intermezzo: The walk to Paradise Garden (Entr’acte from a village Romeo and Juliet) Wien: Universal-Edition, 1934, 20 p. (Box-folder 20/7)
  - Dello Joio, Norman
    - To a lone sentry: for solo piccolo, clarinet, trumpet, and brass, percussion, and strings. [S.l.: s.n.], 1943, Photocopy; 14 p. (Box-folder 59/3)
  - Diamond, David
    - [Rounds, string orchestra]
      - Rounds for string orchestra, 1944. Philadelphia: Elkan-Vogel, 1946, 44 p. (Box-folder 20/8)
  - Donovan, Richard
    - [Ricercare, oboe, string orchestra]
      - Ricercare for oboe and string orchestra. [S.l.: s.n., n.d.], Photocopy; 18 p. (Box-folder 21/1)
  - Dubensky, Arcady
    - Fanfare. New York: G. Ricordi, 1939, Full score and parts; Introduction to the “Star Spangled Banner.” (Box-folder 21/2)
  - Duke, Vernon
    - Concerto (G) for violin solo and orch[estra] [S.l.: s.n.], 1940-41, Photocopy; 72 p.; Reduction for violin and piano. (Box-folder 21/3)
  - Dvořák, Antonín
    - Neue Slavische Tänze: (Dritte Sammlung) Leipzig: Röder’schen Offloin, [n.d.], Photocopy; 114 p.; Op. 72 Heft I. (Box-folder 21/4)
    - Neue Slavische Tänze: (Vierte Sammlung) Leipzig: Röder’schen Offloin, [n.d.], Photocopy; 110 p.; Op. 72, Heft II. (Box-folder 21/5)
    - [Slovanské tance, op. 46]
      - Slavische Tänze. Leipzig: Röder’schen Offloin, [n.d.], Photocopy; 136 p.; Op. 46, Heft II. (Box-folder 21/6)
    - [Symphony, no. 8, op. 88, G major]
      - Symphonie nr. 4, in G-dur, op. 88. Leipzig: Musikwissenschaftlicher Verglag, 1941, 106 p. (Box-folder 21/7)
  - Fairchild, Blair
    - A Bel-ebat. Paris: Durand & Cie., 1937, 9 p.; V. 2 Midi Sous Les Ormes. (Box-folder 22/1)
  - Finn, William Joseph
    - Orchestral settings of five a cappella numbers of the 16th century. New York: William J. Finn, 1938, 63 p. (Box-folder 22/2)
  - Fitelberg, Jerzy
    - Nocturne for orchestra. [S.l.: s.n.], 1944, Photocopy; 63 p. (Box-folder 59/4)
    - Polish pictures: suite for orchestra. [S.l.: s.n.], 1946, Photocopy; 105 p. (Box-folder 22/3)
  - Foss, Lukas
    - Piano concerto no. 2. New York: Carl Fischer Inc., 1953, Photocopy; 148 p. (Box-folder 53/1)
    - The song of songs: second biblical solo cantata: in 4 movements for soprano and orchestra. [S.l.: s.n.], 1946, Photocopy; 31 p. (Box-folder 22/4)
  - Frederiksen, Sigurd
    - Sailor Sail your luck: overture on a sea-chantey. [S.l.: s.n., n.d.], Holograph; 39 p.; Translated by S.F. (Box-folder 22/5)
  - Fuga, Sandro
    - [Concerto sacro. Vocal score. Latin]
      - Concerto sacro: riduzione per canto e pianoforte. Milano: Edizioni Suvini Zerboni, 1949, 61 p. (Box-folder 22/6)
  - Fuleihan, Anis
    - Three Cyprus serenades for orchestra. [S.l.: s.n., n.d.], Photocopy; 61 p.; Previously titled Divertimento [front cover and title page]. (Box-folder 53/2)
  - Gabrieli, Giovanni
    - [Untitled] [S.l.: s.n., n.d.], Photocopy; p. 15, 18; Folder contained address for Hans David. (Box-folder 22/7)
  - Gargiulo, Terenzio
    - Sinfonia (1953) [S.l.: s.n.], 1953, Photocopy; 182 p. (Box-folder 53/3)
  - Gaul, Harvey B.
    - [Palestinian pastels]
      - Three Palestinian pastels, for string orchestra. New York: J. Fischer & Bro., [1935], 41 p. (Box-folder 22/8)
  - George, Earl
    - Introduction and allegro for orchestra. [S.l.: s.n.], 1946, Photocopy; 63 p. (Box-folder 53/4)
  - Gnecchi, Vittorio
    - [Missa Salisburgensis. Vocal Score. Latin]
      - Missa Salisburgensis: fur Sopransolo, gemischten Chor und Orchester. Wien: Universal-Edition, 1934, 81 p. (Box-folder 22/9)
  - Goossens, Eugene, Sir
    - [Symphonies, no. 1, op. 58]
      - First Symphony, opus 58. New York: Carl Fischer Inc., 1942, 155 p. (Box-folder 23/1)
  - Gould, Morton
    - Minstrel show. New York: G. & C. Music Corp., 1936, Photocopy; 32 p. (Box-folder 23/2)
  - Graener, Paul
    - [Gotische Suite, orchestra, op. 74]
      - Gotische Suite. Berlin: Ed. Bote & G. Bock, 1926, 37 p. (Box-folder 23/3)
    - [Schwedische Tänze]
      - Drei Schwedische Tänze. Berlin: Ed. Bote & G. Bock, 1932, 22 p. (Box-folder 23/4)
  - Grieg, Edvard
    - [Peer Gynt. Suite, no. 2]
      - Suite: der Brautraub Bruderovet (Ingrids Klage) la plainte d’Ingrid, op. 55. New York: Edwin F. Kalmus, [n.d.], Photocopy; 57 p. (Box-folder 23/5)
  - Haieff, Alexei
    - [Divertimento, orchestra]
      - Divertimento. [S.l.: s.n.], 1944, Photocopy; 28 p. (Box-folder 53/5)
  - Handel, George Frideric
    - Allegro sarabande gigue. New York: G. Ricordi & Co., 1941, 14 p.; Transcription for string orchestra by Fabien Sevitzky. (Box-folder 23/6)
    - [Water music. Selections; arr.]
      - Suite from the Water Music (Handel) Suite for orchestra (from the Watermusic) [page 1] London: Murdoch, Murdoch & Co., 1922, Full score and parts; Arranged by Sir Hamilton Harty. (Box-folder 23/7)
  - Harris
    - [Untitled] [S.l.: s.n., n.d.], Photocopy; 27 p. (Box-folder 59/5)
  - Hartmann, Thomas de
    - Symphonie - poème. Paris: Office d’Éditions Musicales, 1936, 311 p. (Box-folder 54/1)
  - Hayden, Joel B. Jr.
    - Fugue in A minor for orchestra. Firenze: Stamp. G. & P. Mignani, 1939, 12 p. (Box-folder 23/8)
  - Hérold, Ferdinand
    - [Zampa. Ouverture]
      - Ouverture für Orchester zur Oper Zampa, order, die Marmorbraut. [S.l.]:Offenbacha/M Joh. André, [n.d.], 42 p. (Box-folder 23/9)
  - Hindemith, Paul
    - Piano concerto. [S.l.: s.n.], 1945, Photocopy; p. 3-86 (Box-folder 24/1)
  - Honegger, Arthur
    - Jeanne d’Arc au Bûcher. Paris: Editions Maurice Senart, [n.d.], Photocopy; 144 p.; Poem by Paul Claudel. (Box-folder 54/2)
    - Prologue pour Jeanne d’Arc au Bucher. New York: Editions Salbert, 1947, 15 p.; Poëme de Paul Claudel. (Box-folder 24/2)
  - Hovhaness, Alan
    - Symphony, no. 1, op. 17 Exile symphony no. I [front cover] New York: Whitney Blake Music Pub., 1939, 36 p.; Limited manuscript edition. (Box-folder 24/3)
  - Ifukube, Akiar
    - [Nihon kyōsōkyoku]
      - Japanese rhapsody. Tokyo: Ryuginsha; New York: G. Schirmer Inc., 1937, 68 p. (Box-folder 54/3)
  - Inghelbrecht, Désiré Emile
    - La nursery: 3e Recueil six pièces enfantines. Paris: Alphonse Leduc, 1920, 55 p. (Box-folder 24/4)
  - Ives, Charles
    - [Holidays. Decoration Day]
      - Decoration Day. [S.l.: s.n., n.d.], 29 p.; Second movement in a set of pieces for orchestra “Holidays in a Connecticut Country Town.” (Box-folder 24/5)
    - [Symphonies, no. 3]
      - 3rd Symphony Third Symphony [front cover] [S.l.: s.n., n.d.], Photocopy; 80 p. (Box-folder 54/4)
  - Jacobi, Frederick
    - Concerto for violoncello und orchestra. Wien: Universal-Edition A.G., 1933, 45 p. (Box-folder 24/6)
  - Jarecki, Tadeusz
    - Chimère: poème symphonique, op. 26. New York: Carl Fischer Inc., 1928, 22 p. (Box-folder 24/7)
  - Jerger, Wilhelm
    - Partita für Orchester, op. 21. Berlin: Ries & Erler G.M.B.H., 1934, 31 p. (Box-folder 24/8)
  - Jirák, Karel Boleslav
    - [Symphonic variations]
      - Symfonické variace, op. 40. Praha: Hudební matice umělecké besedy, 1947, 82 p. (Box-folder 24/9)
  - Kabalevsky, Dmitry Borisovich
    - [Kola Briun ́on. Suite]
      - Kola Briun ́on: Master iz Klamsi: opera po Romėn Rollanu: siuita dliabol ́shogo orkestra = Colas Breugnon: Maître de Clamecy: opéra d’aprés Romain Rolland: suite pour grand orchestre. Moskva: Gosudarstvennoe Muzykal’noe Izd-vo., 1941, 168 p.; Op. 24. (Box-folder 24/10)
  - Kalniņš, Alfrēds
    - [Banuta. Levads]